Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-256
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Notebook of a garment worker - citizen, Publication (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The thread of life; ILGWU health and welfare services., 1956; Publication (Box 198, Folder 5)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Why worry?, Publication (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Legislative representation in New York State, 1957; Publication (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Legislative representation in New York State; a discussion of a vital constitutional issue before the voters of New York State. October 1957, Publication (Box 198, Folder 6)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Fundamental principles underlying the protocol, Publication (Box 198, Folder 7)
    Author: John A. Dyche
  - Item 2: Protocol of peace between the Dress and Waist manufacturers' Association and the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1913; Publication (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Protocol of peace in the dress and waist industry, 1913; Publication (Box 198, Folder 7)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: correspondence, Publication (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Financial report - ILGWU - sixteenth convention, May 1, 1922, Publication (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Press release, 1962; Publication (Box 198, Folder 8)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: A report on the production standards situation in the ladies' garment industry of Cleveland, 1925; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
    Author: Cleveland Garment Manufacturers' Association
  - Item 2: Activities of the ILGWU Research Dept., 1942; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: An American adventure in workers' education: Charles A. Beard & The Workers' education bureau, 1936; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
    Notes: Reprinted from Workers' Education
  - Item 4: Forty-cent minimum wage for the women's apparel industry, 1941; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: ILGWU, Educational Dept., Bulletin (tenth season), 1926-1927 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: ILGWU, Educational Dept. - Announcement of Courses, 1920-1921 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: In the Circuit Court of Cook County in Chancery: James S. O'Brien et al. vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union; Ash-Madden-Rae Co. et al. vs. International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union et al.: opinion by Judge Jesse A. Baldwin, 1917; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
    Author: Jesse A. Baldwin
  - Item 8: In the matter of the Cleveland Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Dress Industry, report of miller, Franklin & Basset, 1920; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Memorandum on the proposals for amendment of the New York Unemployment Ins. Law, submitted to the Unemployment insurance state advisory council, Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: The Women's garment workers, 1924; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
    Author: Louis Levine
  - Item 11: This thing called productivity, 1948; Publication (Box 199, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Aspects of industrial homework in apparel trades, 1941; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Central School 1936-1937 - Course - Unionism and the mass production industries, Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Local 22
  - Item 3: Commentary on the report of the price statistics review committee, 1961; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Conditions in the women's garment industry, 1970; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Research Dept.
  - Item 5: Conditions in the women's garment industry, 1961; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
    Notes: Statistics
  - Item 6: Statement of Lazare Teper, 1949; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: The Women's garment industry of Canada: the past decade and current outlook, 1961; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Utilization of price indexes in private and public policy decisions, 1966; Publication (Box 199, Folder 2)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A reprint from an Appraisal of the 1950 census income data, Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Activities of the ILGWU Research Dept., 1942; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Bulletin for organizers and active members on the new wage-hour law, Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Conditions in the Women's Garment industry, 1955; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Management and labor make strong medicine, 1947; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
    Notes: Reprint Occupational Hazards. 2 copies
  - Item 6: Memorandum on seasonal determination in unemployment insurance, 1939; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: New York Unemployment insurance law as amended in 1955, Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Prices and steady economic growth: an issue in public policy formulation, 1958; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Statement of Lazare Teper, 1949; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: United States imports of foreign-made women's and children's garments, 1959; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Wage dilemma: an address delivered by Lazare Teper, 1947; Publication (Box 199, Folder 3)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: After a life of labor: a pioneering union's program for retirees, Publication (Box 199, Folder 4)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Retiree Service Dept.
  - Item 2: For Senior Citizens: The Friendly Visitor, 1969; Publication (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Retire and remembered, Publication (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: why friendly visiting, Publication (Box 199, Folder 4)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: South Bronx Garment Workers News, Publication (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Supplement to the Bulletin - Adding Years to Life, 1956; Publication (Box 199, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.3:supplement no.1. Copy 2
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Southern Garment Worker, 1966; Publication (Box 199, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.1:no.5
  - Item 2: Southern Garment Worker, 1966-1967 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.2:no.1-4,6
  - Item 3: Southern Garment Worker, 1967; Publication (Box 199, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1- 2
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Home town union: the story of the ILGWU in Fall River and Vicinity, 1948; Publication (Box 199, Folder 7)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Building and defending democracy, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Labor fights bigotry, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: Let's put more LIFE into union meetings, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Librarians and labor, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: Purging the text books, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: Socialism - is it smear word or a menace?, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: The coming great expansion in public education, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: The constant catfish, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: The pains of private enterprise, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Would leisure be just awful?, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: Freedom and authority in labor unions, 1953; Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
    Notes: Chapter VI of the twelfth symposium of the Conference of Science, Philosophy and Religion
  - Item 12: Garment workers: welfare unionism, 1954; Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
    Notes: Reprint from Current History. 2 copies
  - Item 13: The basis of world organization and labor's contribution to international understanding, 1952; Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
    Notes: Chapter XII of Eleventh Symposium of the Conference on Science, Philosophy and Religion
  - Item 14: The struggle for the schools, Publication (Box 199, Folder 8)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Estructura y funcionamiento de la ILGWU, 1947-1950 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 2: Structure and functioning of the ILGWU, 1955; Publication (Box 199, Folder 9)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The ILGWU training institute., 1956; Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: Tips for organizers, Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
    Author: Glaser, Henry; ILGWU Training Institute
  - Item 3: Training for union service, Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
    Author: ILGWU Training Institute
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Problems, Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
    Author: Sessions, Jack; ILGWU Training Institute
  - Item 5: Course of study, Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Item 6: Preparing for a career in labor leadership, Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
  - Item 7: Proceedings, third Leadership Training Institute, 1957; Publication (Box 199, Folder 10)
    Author: Union Leadership Institute
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Your union health center, Publication (Box 200, Folder 1)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Information relative to the letter of April 7, 1947, concerning the decision of the General Exec. Bd. Of the Union Health Center, Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
    Notes: Press release
  - Item 2: In-hospital surgical and medical expense identity, 1946; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Medical examination health information, 1925; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Report of the Union Health Center to the 23rd convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, 1937; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
    Author: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union. Union Health Center
  - Item 5: The Union Dental Clinic, 1918; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: The Union Health Center: health, medical and dental service for workers, 1934; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Union Health Center: Report to the 24th convention of the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, May, 1940, New York, N.Y., Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Union Health Center: ceremonies and inspection of facilities marking completion of expansion program, 1949; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Union health center of the ILGWU, 1953; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
    Notes: Reprinted from Industrial Medicine and Surgery, Oct. 1953. 2 copies
  - Item 10: Union Health Center, Interim report, 1944-1945 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: Union Health Center, report to 1922 convention, Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Union Health Center, Triennial report, 1944-1946 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Workers and their teeth troubles, 1927; Publication (Box 200, Folder 2)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Your union is the ILGWU, 1953; Publication (Box 200, Folder 3)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A guide for shop meetings, Publication (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Upstate New York and Vermont District Institute, ILGWU, 1960; Publication (Box 200, Folder 4)
    Author: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell Univ.
    Notes: conference booklet of miscellaneous information
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Seamlines, 1957; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.1:no.4-7, 10, 12
  - Item 2: Seamlines, 1958; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.2:no.4
  - Item 3: Seamlines, 1959; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.3:no.1, 4
  - Item 4: Seamlines, 1960; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.4:no.3-4
  - Item 5: Seamlines, 1961; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.5:no.3-4
  - Item 6: Seamlines, 1962; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.6:no.4
  - Item 7: Seamlines, 1963; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.7:no.4
  - Item 8: Seamlines, 1964; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.8:no.2-4
  - Item 9: Seamlines, 1965; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol.9:no.3,6
  - Item 10: Seamlines, 1966; Publication (Box 200, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. [10]:no.1,3
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Your trousseau and how to plan it, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Ready to serve, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: The Label and you, 1961-1962 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    Notes: conference folder
  - Item 4: Travel in style, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Fashion flash, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: How to be well dressed, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: How to dress your little girl, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Meet Janie - one of America's best dressed women to be, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Mother-Daughter guide to fashion, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: There's a story in those seams, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: Travel in style, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: Your dream wardrobe, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: Your dream wardrobe, Publication (Box 200, Folder 6)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Financial report of the Health, welfare and retirement funds, 1958; Publication (Box 200, Folder 7)
    Notes: Jan. 1, 1958-Dec. 31, 1958
  - Item 2: Health & Welfare fund forms, Publication (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: Health and welfare funds in the needle trades, 1951; Publication (Box 200, Folder 7)
    Author: Adolph Held
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Aspects of industrial homework in apparel trades, 1941; Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: correspondence, 1936; Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, suggestions for social, educational and recreational program for our local unions, 1934; Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Method and approach in a discussion of the economics of the garment industry for young workers ..., 1937; Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Item 5: The International ladies' garment workers' union and workers' education, 1926; Publication (Box 200, Folder 8)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Method and approach in a discussion of the economics of the garment industry for young workers ..., 1937; Publication (Box 200, Folder 9)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: How Canadian labour laws affect us and our union, 1952; Publication (Box 201, Folder 1)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Union says Rubinstein contract extended, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
    Notes: Newspaper clipping
  - Item 2: 700 gas strikers defy Milwaukee Court order, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Atom plant workers obey injunction, stay on job, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Atom strike threat at Oak Ridge eased, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Conferees reach atom strike pact, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Eisenhower moves to end atom tie-up, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Inquiry is rushed in atomic strikes, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Lab workers vote against CIO tie, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: No place for a strike, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 10: Paducah atom strike ends as workers reverse stand, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 11: President seeks atom strike writ, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Sir H. Williams British M.P., 69, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Strike at Monsanto Plant in Michigan halts production, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 14: Strike halts work on south side to county gas line, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 15: Strike threat hits plasma campaign, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 16: Union merger opposed, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 17: Union pact averts halting of plasma, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 18: Union seeks rise in dues, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 19: 3200 at Oak Ridge get a wage increase, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 20: Gas union re-elects Swisher, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 21: High court to hear strike ban attack, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Item 22: Pact ends gas strike, 1954; Publication (Box 201, Folder 2)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The District 3 Courier, 1953; Publication (Box 201, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol.1:no.1,2 (1953)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: For United-CIO stewards, Publication (Box 201, Folder 4)
    Author: United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America
  - Item 2: How to conduct your union meeting, Publication (Box 201, Folder 4)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Executive Board hearing, 1953; Publication (Box 201, Folder 5)
    Notes: Has a note attached, Do Not Circulate, so not cataloged
  - Item 2: International Executive Board Meeting, 1952; Publication (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Report of International Executive Board Meeting, 1953; Publication (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Statement of policy, 1947; Publication (Box 201, Folder 5)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers coming apart at the seams, Publication (Box 201, Folder 6)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Light, 1953; Publication (Box 201, Folder 7)
    Notes: (March, 1953)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: The Bugle, 1951; Publication (Box 201, Folder 8)
    Notes: vol.3:no.31 (1951)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Souvenir program, 4th Annual picnic, 1947; Publication (Box 201, Folder 9)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Why? When? Where? What? Who?, 1944; Publication (Box 201, Folder 10)
    Author: United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America. Local 194
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: U.S. Dept. of Labor, Report and recommendations of the fact finding board appointed by order of the Secretary of Labor, 1946; Publication (Box 201, Folder 11)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Report to the sixth constitutional convention, United Gas, Coke & Chemical Workers of America, CIO, 1952; Publication (Box 201, Folder 12)
    Author: Cecil Martin
  - Item 2: Report to the sixth constitutional convention, United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America, CIO., 1952; Publication (Box 201, Folder 12)
    Author: Martin Wagner and Joseph Joy
    Notes: Martin Wagner, International President. Joseph Joy, International Vice-President
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: from: Martin Wagner, President - to: Regional Directors International Representatives, 1948; Publication (Box 201, Folder 13)
    Author: Martin Wagner
    Notes: Re: Reports on NLRB cases, law suits, etc. 2 copies
  - Item 2: from: The Office of the International Pres. Prepared by Attorney Benjamin C. Sigal - to: All Executive Board Members, International Representatives, and Local Unions, 1947; Publication (Box 201, Folder 13)
    Author: Benjamin C. Sigal
    Notes: Preliminary instructions regarding operations under the Taft-Hartley Act
  - Item 3: Memo- from: Martin Wagner, President -- to: Staff members and Local Unions, 1947; Publication (Box 201, Folder 13)
    Notes: Re: Filing of Taft-Hartley registration forms and affidavits. 2 copies
  - Item 4: Statement of President Wagner concerning removal of Vice Presidents Ross and Doyle from the union payroll, 1947; Publication (Box 201, Folder 13)
- UGC (United Gas, Coke and Chemical Workers of America), Publication (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The steward's job in UGC & CWA-CIO, Publication (Box 201, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: We handle your grievances, Publication (Box 201, Folder 14)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 100 years, 1977; Publication (Box 202, Folder 1)
    Author: Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada
  - Item 2: 100th Anniversary booklet, 1977; Publication (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Our Home - brochure about new headquarters, Publication (Box 202, Folder 1)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Glass workers negotiate, 1954; Publication (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Report of President Lee W. Minton to the 62nd convention of the Glass Bottle Blowers Association, Los Angeles, California, 1961; Publication (Box 202, Folder 2)
    Author: Lee W. Minton
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Report of National President John A. Voll to the Forty-First Annual Convention of the Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Detroit, Michigan, July Twelfth, Nineteen- seventeen., 1917; Publication (Box 202, Folder 3)
    Author: John A. Voll
  - Item 2: Wage scale and working rules of the Glass Bottle Blowers' Association of the United States and Canada: Machine; Season of 1917-1918, Publication (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: In Memoriam, Denis A. Hayes, Pres. Of the Glass., 1917; Publication (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Memo, Publication (Box 202, Folder 3)
- Glass Bottle Blowers Association of the United States and Canada, Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A contemporary analysis of a labor union, 1959; Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
    Author: Miles E. Hoffman
    Notes: Labor monograph, no.1. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Agenda area educational conference, 1955; Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
    Notes: Spring 1955
  - Item 3: Collective bargaining at its best, 1955; Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Glass Horizons, 1953; Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Technological unemployment, 1932; Publication (Box 202, Folder 4)
    Author: James Maloney